Solley mss., 1888-2006 LMC 2885
Lilly Library
- Automobile Catalogs
  - Great Britain
    - Bentley, "Bentley – The Silent Sports Car", 1938 (Jan. 26) (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Third Degree" by M. Tombs, 1939 (Feb. 10) (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "The 4¼ Litre Bentley Mark VI", 1946 (May 24) (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Abridged Particulars of Bentley (Mark VI)", 1946; (3 copies) (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Guarantee" (Solley's 4¼ Litres Mark VI), 1948 (Aug. 12) (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Bentley Mark VI Four–and–a–Quarter Litre", 1949 (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "The Continental", c. 1950s (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Bentley Mark VI Four–and–a–Quarter Litre", 1950 (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Bentley, Mark Six Silent Sports Car", 1952; (2 copies) (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Silent Sports Car", 1952 (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Fully Automatic Gear Box", c. 1953 (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Bentley", 1954 (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "The Bentley Cresta", 1948–1949 (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "The Bentley Continental", 1956 (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Bentley – 'S' Series", 1957 (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "The Bentley Continental", c. 1959 (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Bentley 'S' Series", c. 1959 (Box 6)
    - Bentley, "Bentley Continental", c. 1962 (Box 7)
    - Bentley, "Bentley Continental", 1963 (Box 7)
    - Bentley, "The How and Where of the 8–Litre Bentleys", c. 1985 (Box 7)
    - Bentley, "Bentley Continental R", 1991 (Box 7)
    - Bentley, "Rolls–Royce and Bentley (1931) Sales Literature (1905-1965)", 1991 (Box 7)
    - Bentley, "Rolls–Royce and Bentley (1931) Sales Literature (1905-1965)" Rev. version, 2000 (Aug.) (Box 7)
    - Bentley, "Bentley Continental Sports Saloon" by Hueber, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Bentley, Photographs (Box 7)
    - Bentley, Renderings (Box 7)
    - Bentley, Road Tests (Box 7)
    - Bentley, Misc. (Box 7)
    - Bristol, Road Tests (Box 7)
    - Brough Superior, "Brough Superior"(SE: 1/1237), c. 1937 (Box 7)
    - Brough Superior, Photographs (Box 7)
    - B.S.A., Road Tests (Box 7)
    - Burney, Misc. (Box 7)
    - Car Mart Ltd., "Permanent Exhibit", c. 1920s (Box 7)
    - Daimler Motor Co., Ltd., "The Daimler Motor Co., Limited"(SE: 1/27), 1897 (Box 7)
    - Daimler, "Daimler"(SE: 6/198), 1909 (Box 7)
    - Daimler, "Specifications...List 1912–5", 1912 (May 30) (Box 7)
    - Daimler, "Specifications...List 1912–6", 1912 (June 30) (Box 7)
    - Daimler, "Daimler"(SE: 7/199), 1913 (Box 7)
    - Daimler, "The Car of the Year"(SE: 9/519), 1926 (Box 7)
    - Daimler, "The Daimler Double-Six '30'"(SE: 10/892a), 1930 (Sept. 1) (Box 7)
    - Daimler, "Another Remarkable Daimler", 1930 (Sept. 19) (Box 7)
    - Daimler, "'20' '40' Daimler '25' '50'", 1933 (Box 7)
    - Daimler, "The Daimler 'Double Six'", 1933 (Box 7)
    - Daimler, "Daimler Vogue", c. 1939 (Box 7)
    - Daimler, "Daimler Straight Eight"(SE: 13/1240), 1939 (Box 7)
    - Daimler, "Straight–Eight and Twenty–Seven", c. 1940s (Box 7)
    - Daimler, "Daimler 'Straight Eight' and 'Twenty–Seven", 1948–1949 (Box 7)
    - Daimler, "Daimler and Lanchester", 1949 (Box 7)
    - Daimler, "Daimler", 1950 (Box 7)
    - Daimler, Photographs (Box 7)
    - Daimler, Renderings (Box 7)
    - Daimler, Road Tests (Box 7)
    - Daimler, Misc. (Box 7)
    - De Lorean, Misc. (Box 7)
    - Dunkley, "A Little Guide to Motor Cars", c. 1897 (Box 7)
    - Ensign, Misc. (Box 7)
    - Frazer Nash, "The New Frazer Nash", 1931 (Box 7)
    - Frazer Nash, "Frazer Nash", 1936–1937 (Box 7)
    - Frazer Nash, Road Tests (Box 7)
    - Frazer Nash, Misc. (Box 7)
    - Frazer Nash BMW, "Type 326 Saloon", 1937–1938 (Box 7)
    - Frazer Nash BMW, "Type 328 Grand Prix Sports Model", 1937–1938 (Box 7)
    - G.N., Road Tests (Box 7)
    - Healey, Road Tests (Box 7)
    - H.R.G., Road Tests (Box 7)
    - Humber, "Humber, the Imperial & Pullman for 1939"(SE: 5/1242) (Box 7)
    - Humber, Photographs (Box 7)
    - Humber, Road Tests (Box 7)
    - Humber, Misc. (Box 7)
    - Invicta, "Invicta"(SE: 1/520), 1926 (Box 7)
    - Invicta, "Invicta"(SE: 3/895a), c. 1931 (Box 7)
    - Invicta, "The Most Wonderful Performance in the World"(SE: 6/1244), 1933 (Box 7)
    - Invicta, "Invicta"(SE: 7/1245), 1938 (Box 7)
    - Invicta, "The Invicta Car", 1946 (Box 7)
    - Invicta, "Invicta...Black Prince", c. 1948 (Box 7)
    - Invicta, Misc. (Box 7)
    - Jensen, "Jensen Motors Ltd."(SE: 1/1246), 1937 (Box 7)
    - Jensen, "Jensen Motors Ltd."(SE: 1/1247), 1939 (Box 7)
    - Jensen, Road Tests (Box 7)
    - Jensen, Misc. (Box 7)
    - Jowett, Road Tests (Box 7)
    - Lagonda, "Lagonda"(SE: 5/1250), 1934 (Box 7)
    - Lagonda, "Lagonda"(SE: 6/1251), 1935 (Box 7)
    - Lagonda, "The Finest of Fast Cars", 1937 (Box 7)
    - Lagonda, "The New Twelve Cylinder..."(SE: 10/1255), 1938 (Box 7)
    - Lagonda, "Cars for 1939"(SE: 11/1256) (Box 7)
    - Lagonda, "Cruising at 97.24 m.p.h....", 1939 (Box 7)
    - Lagonda, "2½ Litre Saloon & Coupe", 1949 (Box 7)
    - Lagonda, "Saloon and Drophead Coupe", 1949 (Box 7)
    - Lagonda, "The David Brown Lagonda Rapide", c. 1960s (Box 7)
    - Lagonda, Photographs (Box 7)
    - Lagonda, Road Tests (Box 7)
    - Lagonda, Misc. (Box 7)
    - Lanchester, "Detail Specifications...12–H.P. Lanchester"(SE: 1/202) (photocopy), 1905 (Box 7)
    - Lanchester, "Lanchester...28–H.P. 6–Cylinder"(SE: 3/204) (photocopy), 1906 (Box 7)
    - Lanchester, "Lanchester Cars"(SE: 6/207), c. 1912 (Box 7)
    - Lanchester, "Lanchester"(SE: 10/522), 1921 (Nov.) (Box 7)
    - Lanchester, "Lanchester 'Forty' Press Opinions"(SE: 11/523), 1922 (Box 7)
    - Lanchester, "The Lanchester 'Forty'", 1923 (Nov.) (Box 7)
    - Lanchester, "Lanchester", 1924 (Oct.) (Box 7)
    - Lanchester, "40 H.P. 6–Cyl Lanchester Car"(SE: 14/526), 1925–1926 (Box 7)
    - Lanchester, Road Tests (Box 7)
    - Lanchester, Misc. (Box 7)
    - Leyland, "The Leyland 'Eight'"(SE: 1/527), 1921 (Box 7)
    - Leyland, "The Leyland 'Eight'"(SE: 2/528), 1922–1923 (Box 7)
    - Leyland, Misc. (Box 7)
    - Lotus, Road Tests (Box 7)
    - Lotus, Misc. (Box 7)
    - Marauder, Road Tests (Box 8)
    - M.G., "Safety Fast! Detailed...M.G. Midget..."(SE: 2/1258b), 1933 (Oct.) (Box 8)
    - M.G., "Safety Fast! Magnette"(SE: 2/1258a), 1933 (Oct.) (Box 8)
    - M.G., "MG Two–Litre"(SE: 3/1259a), 1936 (Box 8)
    - M.G., "MG Two–Litre"(SE: 3/1259b), 1936 (Sept. 21) (Box 8)
    - M.G., "MG Midget Series 'T'"(SE: 4/1260), c. 1937 (Box 8)
    - M.G., "MG Two–Litre", 1937–1938 (Box 8)
    - M.G., "MG Two–Litre"(SE: 5/1261), 1939 (Box 8)
    - M.G., Road Tests (Box 8)
    - M.G., Misc. (Box 8)
    - Morgan, Road Tests (Box 8)
    - Morgan, Misc. (Box 8)
    - Morris, Road Tests (Box 8)
    - Napier, "Napier, London, New York, Boston"(SE: 2/211), 1905–1906 (Box 8)
    - Napier, "Napier"(SE: 3/212), 1907 (Box 8)
    - Napier, "Noiseless Napier Motors All British"(SE: 4/213), 1910 (Box 8)
    - Napier, "Noiseless Napier Motors"(SE: 5/214), 1911 (Box 8)
    - Napier, "The Napier Book"(SE: 9/531), 1924 (Box 8)
    - Napier, Misc. (Box 8)
    - Railton, "Railton", c. 1937–1938 (Box 8)
    - Riley, "The M.P.H"(SE: 1/1262), 1934–1935 (Box 8)
    - Riley, "For Enthusiasts Only..."(SE: 2/1263), 1938 (Box 8)
    - Riley, "Riley", 1949 (Box 8)
    - Riley, Photographs (Box 8)
    - Riley, Road Tests (Box 8)
    - Riley, Misc. (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "1905. The New All-British Motor Car"(SE: 1/216) (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce"(SE: 3/218) (1961 reprint), 1906 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce"(SE: 4/219), 1906–1907 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "The Ideal Car"(SE: 6/221), 1908–1909 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce"(SE: 7/222a), 1909 (Mar.) (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce"(SE: 9/224), 1911–1912 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce"(SE: 10/225), 1912–1913 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce"(SE: 11/226), 1912–1913 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Derniers Succes 1913" (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce"(SE: 12/227a), 1914 (Jan.) (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce", c. 1920s (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Renderings", c. 1921 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce from the Owner–Driver's Point of View", 1922 (May 10) (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce Six–Cylinder 20 h.p. Car", c. 1922–1923 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce 20 H.P."(SE: 16/535), 1922–1923 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "The Charm of the 20 H.P. Rolls–Royce", 1923 (July 3) (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, Rolls–Royce correspondence, 1924–1960 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce Twenty H.P. Six Cylinder"(SE: 16/535a), c. 1924; (2 copies) (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "The Inheritance of Rolls–Royce", 1926 (June) (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "The 20 H.P. Rolls–Royce", 1927 (Oct. 10) (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "20 H.P. Six–Cylinder Tourer–De–Luxe", c. 1928 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "The 20 H.P. Rolls–Royce", 1928 (Oct.) (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce – El Mejor Coche Del Mundo", 1928–1929 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "20 H.P. Rolls–Royce Weymann Saloon"(flyer), c. 1928–1929 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Specification...Phantom II 40–50 H.P. Chassis", 1929 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "The 20 H.P. Six Cylinder", 1929 (June) (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Phantom II"(SE: 23/905), 1929–1930 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Phantom II – Continental Touring Saloon"(reprint), c. 1930 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Phantom II"(SE: 24/906), 1931–1932 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "My New Rolls–Royce", 1932 (Apr. 16) (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "An Entirely New Rolls–Royce Gearbox", 1932 (July 26) (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce Modifications", 1932 (July 29) (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Phantom II"(SE: 25/1264), 1933 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "The 20–l25 H.P.", 1932–1933 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "The 20–25 H.P. Rolls–Royce", c. 1934 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Phantom II"(SE: 26/1265b), 1934–1935 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Handbook for 40–50 H.P....(Phantom II)", c. 1935 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "The 20–25 H.P.", 1935 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce Phantom III – Catalogue Abrege", c. 1935–1936 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "20/25 H.P. Rolls–Royce"(announcement), 1936 (Apr. 16) (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Phantom III"(SE: 27/1266a), 1935–1936 (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "The 40–50 H.P. Rolls–Royce Phantom III", 1936 (Sept. 29) (Box 8)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Phantom III"(SE: 28/1267), 1937–1938 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "The 25–30 H.P. Rolls–Royce", c. 1937–1938 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "The 25–30 H.P....'Wraith'"(abridged catalogue), 1938 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Phantom III – World's Fair, New York", 1939 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "The 25–30 H.P", 1937–1938 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "The 25–30 H.P....The 'Wraith'"(SE: 29/1268), 1938 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "'Wraith – 25–30 ' CV", c. 1939 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "...Silver Wraith", 1946 (Apr. 5) (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce Silver Wraith", 1946 (Apr. 5) (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "...Silver Wraith"(abridged catalogue), 1946 (May 16); (2 copies) (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Silver Wraith, Drophead Foursome Coupe"(photocopy), 1946 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Silver Wraith Drophead Foursome Coupe"(original and photocopy), 1947 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Showing the Flag", 1947 (Oct. 15) (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Silver Dawn", 1949 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "...Silver Wraith", 1949 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Royal Rolls–Royce", 1950 (July 7) (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, Rolls–Royce 'Silver Wraith': Abridged Particulars", 1950 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Silver Dawn" 1950 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Album of Sales – V. 1 British Rolls", 1953 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Album of Sales – V. 2 American Rolls", 1951 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Silver Dawn", 1952 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Silver Dawn", 1952–1953 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Silver Dawn", 1953 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Silver Dawn", 1953 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Abridged Particulars – Silver Wraith", 1953 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce/Bentley", 1953 (Aug. 7) (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce", 1953–1954 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Silver Wraith", 1956–1957 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Silver Wraith", 1957 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "The Silver Cloud", 1958 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce/Bentley", c. 1960s (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce Silver Ghost – Book of Instruction...Care", 1960 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce & Bentley", 1962 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Silver Cloud III", 1963 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce", 1967 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce", c. 1970s (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Phantom VI Specs.", 1971 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce in America"(facsimile reprint, 1971), c. 1920s (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Phantom VI Special Laudalette", 1972 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Phantom VI", 1973 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Handbook Part I for 20–25 H.P. Rolls–Royce Car"(reprint), 1976 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "The Achievement of Excellence", 1977 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce: Fact and Legend" by C.S. Shoup(2nd ed.), 1979 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce: Fact and Legend" by C.S. Shoup(3rd ed.), 1988 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce Owners' Club – 33rd National Meet – Lancaster, PA", 1984 (Sept.) (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce Owners' Club – 34th National Meet – Toronto, Canada", 1985 (Aug. 21-24) (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce Owners' Club – 35th National Meet – Nashville, TN", 1986 (Sept. 6) (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce Owners' Club – 37th National Meet – Cincinnati, Ohio", 1988 (Aug. 10–14) (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce Owners' Club – 38th National Meet – Newport, R.I.", 1989 (Aug. 8–13) (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "1959 Rolls Royce Silver Wraith for Sale", 1987 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Hose Clamp" (newsletter), 1987–1997 (inc.) (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Robert Jankel Design – Rolls-Royce/Bentley Conversions", 1988 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce Enthusiasts' Club – Concours and Rally – Souvenir Programme Courtenhall near Northampton", 1987 (June 20-21) (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls-Royce Enthusiasts' Club – Concours and Rally – Souvenir Programme, Castle Ashby, Northamptonshire", 1989 (June 17–18) (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce Enthusiasts' Club – Concours and Rally – Souvenir Programme – Castle Ashby, Northamptonshire", 1991 (June 15–16) (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce and Bentley (1931) Sales Literature (1905–1965)", 1991 (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, "Rolls–Royce & Bentley Celebration at Windsor", 2002 (Apr. 27) (Box 9)
    - Rolls–Royce, Renderings (Box 10)
    - Rolls–Royce, Road Tests (Box 10)
    - Rolls–Royce, Negatives and Page Proofs, (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Rolls–Royce, Photographs, (4 folders) (Box 10)
    - Rolls–Royce, Photographs – London Settings, c. 1920s–1930s (Box 10)
    - Rolls–Royce, Misc. (Box 10)
    - Rover, "Rover 1935" (Box 10)
    - Rover, Renderings (Box 10)
    - Rover, Road Tests (Box 10)
    - Rover, Misc. (Box 10)
    - Santler, Misc. (Box 10)
    - Sheffield Simplex, "Sheffield Simplex 1910" (Box 10)
    - Sheffield Simplex, "Sheffield Simplex"(SE: 4/231), 1914 (Box 10)
    - Sheffield Simplex, Misc. (Box 10)
    - Shelsley Motors Ltd, "Raymond Mays Cars", 1939 (Box 10)
    - Singer, "Airstream Singer Eleven"(SE: 1/1269), 1934 (Box 10)
    - Singer, Road Tests (Box 10)
    - Singer, Misc. (Box 10)
    - Squire, "The Squire Car"(SE: 2/1271a), c. 1934 (Box 10)
    - Squire, "The Squire Car"(SE: 2/1271b), c. 1934 (Box 10)
    - Squire, "New Supercharged Sports Car", 1934 (Sept. 14) (Box 10)
    - Squire, "A New Supercharged Sports Car", 1934 (Oct.) (Box 10)
    - Squire, Photographs (Box 10)
    - Squire, Renderings (Box 10)
    - Squire, Misc. (Box 10)
    - SS and Jaguar, "SS Cars", 1935 (Box 10)
    - SS and Jaguar, "Jaguar", 1936 (Box 10)
    - SS and Jaguar, "Jaguar SS", 1938 (Box 10)
    - SS and Jaguar, "Jaguar", 1940 (Box 10)
    - SS and Jaguar, Photographs (Box 10)
    - SS and Jaguar, Renderings (Box 10)
    - SS and Jaguar, Misc. (Box 10)
    - Sunbeam, "Sunbeam"(SE: 2/539), 1921 (Box 10)
    - Sunbeam, "Sunbeam 'The Supreme Car'"(SE: 3/540), 1926 (Jan.) (Box 10)
    - Sunbeam, "Sunbeam 'The Supreme Car'"(SE: 4/907), 1929 (Box 10)
    - Sunbeam, "Sunbeam 'The Supreme Car'"(SE: 5/908), 1930 (Oct.) (Box 10)
    - Sunbeam, "Sunbeam 'The Supreme Car'"(SE: 6/1273), 1933–1934 (Box 10)
    - Sunbeam, "Sunbeam", 1936–1937 (Box 10)
    - Sunbeam, Road Tests (Box 10)
    - Sunbeam, Misc. (Box 10)
    - Swift, Photographs (Box 10)
    - Talbot, "Coachwork on Talbot..."(SE: 1/1275), 1933 (Box 10)
    - Talbot, "Talbot 'The Invincible'"(SE: 2/1276), 1933–1934 (Box 10)
    - Talbot, "The Book of Talbot"(SE: 3/1277), 1937 (Box 10)
    - Talbot, "Talbot", 1937 (Box 10)
    - Talbot, "Sunbeam – Talbot", 1939 (Box 10)
    - Talbot, Road Tests (Sunbeam – Talbot) (Box 10)
    - Talbot, Misc. (Box 10)
    - Triumph, "Triumph 'Dolomite'"(SE: 1/1278), 1934–1935 (Box 10)
    - Triumph, "Triumph"(SE: 2/1279), 1939 (Box 10)
    - Triumph, "Triumph Dolomite Vitesse", c. 1930s (Box 10)
    - Triumph, Road Tests (Box 10)
    - Triumph, Misc. (Box 10)
    - Vandenplas, Road Tests (Box 10)
    - Vauxhall, "Vauxhall Motor Carriages"(SE: 2/541), 1921 (Nov.) (Box 10)
    - Vauxhall, "Single–Sleeve Six 25–70 Vauxhall"(SE: 5/544), 1926 (Box 10)
    - Vauxhall, "30 – 98 Vauxhall", 1927 (Box 10)
    - Vauxhall, "New Vauxhall 20–60"(SE: 6/909), 1928 (Box 10)
    - Vauxhall, Photographs (Box 10)
    - Vauxhall, Misc. (Box 10)
    - Wolseley, Photographs (Box 10)
    - Wolseley, Road Tests (Box 10)
    - Wolseley, Misc. (Box 10)
    - Alvis, "Speed Twenty"(SE: 2/1209), 1934 (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Alvis, "La plus Aristocrate...'Speed Twenty'", 1936 (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Alvis, "Speed. Twenty. Five"(SE: 7/1214), 1937 (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Armstrong Siddeley, "Siddeley Special"(SE: 7/1218), 1935–1936 (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Bentley, "Bentley Six–and–a–Half Litre Six–Cylinder" No. 27(SE: 12/886), 1928 (Oct.) (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Bentley, "The World's Finest Sporting Car..." No. 33(SE: 14/888), 1929 (Oct.) (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Bentley, "A Detailed Description of the Six Cylinder Four Litre..."(SE: 17/891), 1931 (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Bentley, "Bentley – The Silent Sports Car, 3½ Litre"(SE: 6/1231), 1935–1936 (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Bentley, "Bentley (The Silent Sports Car, 4½ Litre)"(SE: 8/1233), 1936–1937 (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Bentley, "Bentley (The Silent Sports Car, 4¼ Litre)"(SE: 9/1234), 1937–1938; (2 copies) (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Bentley, "The Bentley Continental", 1955 (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Bentley, "Bentley S2 – Four Door Saloon", c. 1958 (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Bentley, "Bentley", c. 1958 (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Bentley, "Bentley 'S' 2", c. 1958 (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Bentley, "Bentley Continental", c. 1960 (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - The Car Mart Ltd., "Carriage Work"(SE: 2/C256), 1939 (Box 25 (Oversize))
    - Daimler, "Daimler 4-Litre Straight Eight"(SE: 12/1239), 1939 (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Lagonda, "Lagonda"(SE: 2/898), 1930 (Mar.) (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Lagonda, "The New 4½ Litre"(SE: 8/1253), 1937 (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Lagonda, "The New 12–Cylinder"(SE: 9/1254), 1937 (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - MG, "Safety Fast!"(SE: 1/901), 1931 (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - H.J. Mulliner Co. Ltd., "Bentley Continental – Four Door Saloon", c. 1960s (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - H.J. Mulliner Co. Ltd., "Bentley Continental – Two Door Saloon", c. 1960s (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Napier, "The Proved Best Car"(SE: 6/215), 1914 (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Napier, "British Built Six Cylinder Motor Carriages"(SE: 7/529), 1920 (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Napier, "British–Built–Six–Cylinder Motor Carriages"(SE: 8/530), 1923 (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - H.R. Owen/Gurney Nutting, "HRO"(SE: 3/C265), 1937 (Oct.) (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Park Ward, "Bentley Continental Coupe", c. 1960s (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "Rolls–Royce 40/50 H.P."(SE: 17/536), 1922–1923 (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "Rolls–Royce 40/50 H.P."(SE: 18/537a), 1923–1924 (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "Rolls–Royce 'New Phantom'"(SE: 19/538), 1925 (Oct. 1) (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "New Phantom"(SE: 20/902), 1927 (Apr. 1) (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "Phantom"(SE: 21/903), 1928 (May 1) (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "Phantom"(SE: 22/904), 1929 (Mar.) (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "The 20–25 H.P. Rolls–Royce", 1931–1932 (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "The 40–50 H.P. Rolls–Royce", 1934 (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "Silver Wraith", c. 1950s (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "Silver Wraith", c. 1950s (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "...Silver Wraith", 1950 (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "Silver Wraith", 1950 (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "Silver Wraith", 1953 (Box 26 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "Phantom V – Park Ward Seven Passenger Limousine", c. 1960s (Box 27 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "Silver Cloud II", c. 1960s (Box 27 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "Silver Cloud II", c. 1960s (Box 27 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "Rolls–Royce Phantom V", c. 1960s (Box 27 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "Rolls–Royce", c. 1960s (Box 27 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "Rolls–Royce Phantom V", 1962–1963 (Box 27 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "Rolls–Royce Silver Cloud III Bentley S3", c. 1963 (Box 27 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "Rolls–Royce & Bentley...", 1963–1964 (Box 27 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "Rolls–Royce, Phantom V", 1963–1964 (Box 27 (Oversize))
    - Rolls-Royce, "Phantom VI", c. 1992 (Box 27 (Oversize))
    - SS and Jaguar, "SS Cars", 1934 (Box 27 (Oversize))
    - Armstrong Siddeley, "The Car of Character", 1950 (Oct.) (Box 30 (Oversize))
    - Atalanta, "Atalanta"(SE: 2/1224), 1938–1939 (Box 30 (Oversize))
    - Bentley, "Blueprints, drawings for various models", c. 1950s–1960s (Box 30 (Oversize))
    - Hooper & Co., "Hooper Motor Carriages", 1923–1924; (2 copies) (Box 33 (Oversize))
    - Hooper & Co, "Specification Design No. 8282– Bentley Chassis", 1950 (Box 34 (Oversize))
  - Holland
    - Duf, Road Tests (Box 10)
    - Spyker, "Spyker Holland" (SE: 2/545), c. 1919 (Box 10)
    - Spyker, "Spyker Six Cylinder 30–40 H.P." (SE: 4/547), 1921 (Box 10)
    - Spyker, Renderings (Box 10)
  - Italy
    - Alfa Romeo, "Ing. Nicola Romeo 'Alfa Romeo' Motor Cars"(SE: 1/548), 1921–1922 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "Alfa-Romeo"(SE: 2/549), 1923-1924 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "Alfa Romeo RM 4 Zylinder..."(SE: 3/550), 1924 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "Alfa-Romeo 6 Cylinder RL"(SE: 4/551), 1924 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "Alfa Romeo"(SE: 9/910), 1926-1927 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "Alfa-Romeo 1500"(SE: 10/911) (photocopy), c. 1927 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "La 1500 Alfa-Romeo"(SE: 11/912), 1928 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "La 1500 Alfa-Romeo"(SE: 12/913), c. 1929 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "VII Alfa-Romeo", 1930 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "6c. Turismo…"(SE: 14/915a), 1931 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "6c. Turismo…"(SE: 14/915d), 1930 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "6c Gran Turismo Compressore"(SE: 15/916), 1931-1932 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "6c Gran Sport"(SE: 16/917), 1931-1932 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "MOD. 8C"(SE: 18/919), 1932 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "6c Gran Turismo Compressore"(SE: 17/918), 1932 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "mod. 8 c. 2300"(SE: 19/1280), 1933 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "Alfa Romeo MOD 8c 2300"(SE: 20/1281), 1933-1934 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "New Alfa Romeo `8C 2900S'"(SE: 21/1282), 1935 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "MOD. 6C .2300. B"(SE: 22/1283), 1936 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "8C 2900 A"(SE: 23/1284), 1936 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "6C. 2300 .B"(SE: 25/1286), 1937 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "8C 2900 B"(SE: 26/1287), 1937 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "8C 2900 B Alfa Romeo"(SE: 27/1288), 1938 (Box 11)
    - Alfa Romeo, "6C 2300 B", 1938 (Box 11)